Hey, before you continue scrolling,
I got a message,
and that message is very simple.
Long story short,
I was basically looking through my drive and I found a bunch of footage
from a long time ago of basically just me doing clips of Valorant.
Like two kills, three kills.
I don't know why I saved these.
I probably was thinking of making a video about them later,
but I guess I just never got around to it.
But anyhow,
here we are.
What's the plan for these?
Now,
originally I was going to think,
you know,
these are useless,
might as well delete these.
But then I thought,
you know,
I might as well use these for my,
editing
help focus thing.
So basically, I'm going to use them as shorts.
So maybe every week,
probably not every week,
but I'll try.
Every week,
until all of these are done,
I will do one clip and one short.
You know, to improve my editing
style and improve my editing period.
But yeah, that's basically it.
Alright,
that's about it.
I'll see you later.
Bye!